<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Estelle and Josh — Two people who like each other</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Estelle and Josh — Two people who like each other</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten</title>
      <link>/story/ten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/ten/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nine</title>
      <link>/story/nine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/nine/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eight</title>
      <link>/story/eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/eight/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven</title>
      <link>/story/seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/seven/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six</title>
      <link>/story/six/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/six/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five</title>
      <link>/story/five/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/five/</guid>
      <description>I returned to San Francisco and several days later went to Burning Man in the vast, isolated Nevada desert. On the second-to-last day I was there, I found a camp that had a cellular internet connection, and I went online and booked a one-way airplane ticket to Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four</title>
      <link>/story/four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/four/</guid>
      <description>This was Estelle&amp;rsquo;s first time at a rooftop bar. It&amp;rsquo;s in Bangkok, where we had one final night to spend together before heading back to our respective homes - Estelle to Paris and I to San Francisco.
Over the last month we&amp;rsquo;d gotten very close - I&amp;rsquo;d never met someone so smart but also so kind. I was worried that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what would come next? Would we ever see each other again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three</title>
      <link>/story/three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/three/</guid>
      <description>After the Mindfulness project, Estelle went to an island called Koh Tao. I joined her there several days later after recovering from a serious illness.
We spent 6 days together on Koh Tao, and that&amp;rsquo;s where we really got to know each other. During the day she&amp;rsquo;d ride behind me on our rented scooter to remote beaches on the island, and at night we&amp;rsquo;d watch dancers spin fire on the beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koh Tao</title>
      <link>/story/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/two/</guid>
      <description>Khon Kaen is the nearest major city to the Mindfulness Project. Once a week, all of the volunteers would visit the city and spend the day meditating at a monastery.
In the evening there was some free time, and Estelle and I would go for a jog around the lake together, stopping for the occasional photo-op with the dinosaur statues lining the path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It began in Thailand</title>
      <link>/story/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/story/one/</guid>
      <description>Estelle and Josh met in Thailand in the summer of 2015 while volunteering at a place called the Mindfulness Project. People from all over the world come to the project to learn about yoga, meditation, Buddhism and permaculture.
One of their first encounters found them creating mud bricks together, as shown here in the first picture. Long stretches of manual labor, also known as karma yoga, afforded volunteers the opportunity to talk at length and get to know each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the Date - July 28, 2018</title>
      <link>/page/save-the-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/save-the-date/</guid>
      <description>Saving soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>